Wait for me!
Good.
Very good.
Really good.
I told you I run fast.
All members are overtime.
All of you
won't have dinner
tonight.
No.
Coach, give us a way out.
Don't worry.
I have plenty of snacks.
Don't be afraid.
I heard that.
I'll give you back the towels.
No, coach.
Take the snacks away.
Give them back to us.
Coach,
why are you suddenly so strict?
The end of the holiday
the official league.
As your coach,
I have to push you harder.
Are you still the coach
we know?
You only know how to play games.
What do you know about pushing harder?
Yeah.
Fine.
Today, I'll give you a chance
to defend your snacks.
Coach,
those are my chips.
what did you mean
by giving us a chance
just now?
Simple.
Each of you will face me one-on-one.
If even one of you
can score just one point against me,
I'll give the snacks back.
That's it?
Just one point?
You're underestimating us!
I knew it!
Coach wouldn't be that cruel!
Who's up?
Me!
Alright.
I've got this.
Don't worry.
Let's start.
Let me tell you,
this one is too easy.
Right.
The snacks will be back in a while.
I really want to eat some.
This is a bit tough.
Next one.
Do you think Zhou Yang will win?
Hard to say.
Next one.
This...
No.
Next.
Next, next.
Come on.
Come on, Gu Chenyang.
Come on, come on, come on.
Oh, no.
Who's next?
How's it going?
Still think I'm just a gamer?
No, no, no.
I challenged you one-on-one
on the one hand,
to show you my strength,
and on the other hand,
I saw
your weaknesses.
From tomorrow,
train hard with me.
Give it your all.
Can you do that?
Yes!
Louder!
Alright, I'm taking the snacks.
Arrange their accommodations.
What are we eating tonight?
We really didn't score a single point.
I didn't expect Coach Su
to be so impressive.
What's his background?
I just looked it up online.
Look.
He was the champion
of the college league,
and the MVP.
That's amazing.
He's so impressive.
Impressive.
He's been keeping a low profile.
Yeah.
Dr. Qin,
I've arrived.
[I'll check in first.]
[I'll come to you later.]
Everyone, look at the camera.
On my mark.
Yibei Basketball Club's retreat.
Love and peace.
Peace!
I'm so hungry.
Go to sleep.
You won't feel hungry when you're asleep.
Li Haoyu has searched.
There's a small supermarket near the base.
There are a lot of delicious food.
Let's go and eat something.
My treat.
We still need to grow.
If you don't want to go, don't go.
The base closes at seven o'clock.
It's already eight o'clock.
You can hear it with your headphones.
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
Let's go.
I asked Xu Anbo.
We can get to the back door of the base
by passing through the swimming pool.
Then we can sneak out from there.
You're really good at doing bad things.
You're reliable.
What?
Zhou Yang.
Why are you here?
I'm out for a night run to get some fresh air.
What are you doing here?
We're just
getting some fresh air
and discussing tactics.
Right, Lin Qingyuan?
Yeah.
Fresh air, huh?
Yeah, let's go.
That's the pool over there.
The dorms are this way.
I know.
That's the swimming pool.
We haven't finished our talk.
We're going to talk at the swimming pool.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Can I go with you?
I also want to talk
about tactics with you.
It's not appropriate.
After all, it's against the rules
to go out at night.
If we take you,
we'll feel uneasy.
Right?
Right.
You are a good student.
If you want to go for food,
you'd better take me.
If you run into Su,
I can cover for you.
Okay.
Let's go.
This place is a bit eerie.
Have you heard
the legend of this natatorium?
What legend?
Ten years ago,
there was an outstanding member of the swimming team.
He swore
to win the national championship.
So he practiced here
until late at night every day.
As a result,
he suddenly got a cramp
in the deep water area.
No one found him.
Then he...
Then what?
Since then, every midnight,
the sound of splashing water
and intermittent crying can be heard here.
Stop, stop it.
Don't listen to him.
It's our first time here.
How can we know
the legend ten years ago?
Yeah, it makes sense.
Li Haoyu, you...
Did you hear that?
What are you afraid of?
How can there be ghosts in this world?
Help! There's a ghost!
Wait a moment.
What are you waiting for? Run!
Go, go, go!
Hurry up!
With your guts,
you dare to go out at night?
Why are you here?
The person at the swimming pool
was you?
Are you a pervert?
You didn't sleep at night,
and pretend to be a ghost in the swimming pool.
I didn't go to the swimming pool.
I went to the coach's office just now
and got you some food.
What's your expression?
It wasn't him just now.
Then just now...
This base
has people from the swimming team.
Maybe it was someone from the swimming team.
Now there's food.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Oh, no.
Where's my gaming console?
Did it
fall into the pool?
Is it the old model?
Aren't you scared?
Let's help him look for it.
This game console is very important
to him.
It was a gift from his mom
on his birthday.
A gift from his mom must be important.
Let's go.
You two,
don't leave me alone.
It's me.
Don't be so startled.
You scared me to death.
Don't be scared.
Hurry up and find it.
Wait.
That crying sound comes again.
That's the wind.
The window is not closed tightly, and there is a crack.
What about that sound?
That's the air conditioner leaking.
I just took the mop
to pad it.
Have you found it?
Not yet.
Don't worry. Let's continue to look for it.
What's that sound?
Fu Bin Yan.
Whose game machine?
Mine.
Come out.
You guys
are really something.
I was just about to fall asleep,
and the security guard called me.
This place
is full of cameras.
Do you really think
you're above the law?
Everyone, run around the base
ten times.
No one gets back to the dorm until it's done.
Ten times?
The security guard is watching you.
Ten laps.
I'm too weak.
Let me eat something first.
If you didn't insist on
going out to eat,
would there be so many things?
Thanks.
Fu Bin Yan,
I didn't have a chance to ask you.
Why are you here?
My mom's client is here.
It happens to be a holiday,
so I came along.
I see.
What a coincidence.
Let's go.
Don't just stand there.
Hurry up and run.
I haven't finished my homework yet.
It won't open.
Let me have a look.
It's okay.
It's an old model anyway.
If it's broken, so be it.
This was a gift from my mom.
I was thinking...
It's really fine.
I have plenty of gaming consoles.
I don't need this one.
Let's go, hurry up and run.
This morning,
we'll do a symbiosis training.
Symbiosis training.
You need to work in pairs,
back to back with a ball,
and cooperate to carry the ball to the baseline.
Lin Qingyuan,
can you slow down a bit?
You're going too fast.
Keep going, don't stop.
Lower your center of gravity a bit.
You're always pushing me.
Let's start over.
Slow down.
Hold steady.
Coach, we're here.
Get ready to shoot.
One person shoots,
the other gives directions.
Follow my lead.
Okay.
This drill tests
your communication
and trust.
A bit more to the right.
To the left, to the left.
Downwards.
Can we throw now?
Too high.
A bit lower.
To the left, to the left.
A bit more...
How did you do?
Zero points.
Next group.
It's too difficult.
Yeah.
It's impossible.
Your turn.
Let's go.
Li Haoyu,
why are you so absent-minded?
No.
Let's go.
What's wrong with your foot?
Nothing, just sprained it a bit.
It's fine.
Excuse me,
is this the Yibei Basketball Team?
Yes.
And you two are...?
Lin and Ye.
Yuan.
Mom also prepared sunscreen for you.
Be sure to use it during outdoor training.
Alright.
We just happened to pass by
to take a look.
Gotta go fishing now.
Yuan.
Train well, be happy every day.
By the way,
I still have something here.
Here we go again with this trick.
Cheer up, cheer up.
We're off.
Brother Lin, Sister Ye.
Good luck fishing.
Wish you a big harvest.
Okay.
Let's go, son.
Bye.
Brother Lin, drive slowly.
Okay.
Your parents are really good to you.
They even thought of bringing you something.
Of course.
Lin and Ye
are like my friends.
Our family's motto is
happiness is the most important.
They just let you do whatever you want?
Yeah.
As long as I'm happy,
they'll support me in everything.
Unlike some people,
who just knows how to recite scriptures.
Xu Anbo.
Let's go eat over there.
Let's go.
Together?
Thank you.
Is Li Haoyu
still like this?
He doesn't tell me.
I don't know what to do.
He's always been like this.
The more you ask, the more he tries to hide it.
Just leave him be.
I'm working on Lin Qingyuan's new plan.
His shortcomings?
Easily distracted, lacks persistence.
That's quite accurate.
Meeting his parents today,
I realized
he must have been
raised with constant encouragement.
Instead of trying to change him,
we should just cater to his interests.
Right?
You're going to encourage him too?
I hope this
will keep him motivated.
Don't worry too much.
Lin Qingyuan may seem
carefree,
but sometimes he's actually
quite focused.
What's the use of temporary focus?
I feel like
I'm talking to a teacher.
Am I?
Insect.
Stay away from me.
Throw it away.
Wait.
What? You like it?
It's called Onthophagus suturalis.
Look at the pattern on its back.
It's pretty.
You know this?
I know a little.
More than a little, I think.
What a person
and what he likes.
Do you have a problem?
- No. - Take it away.
It doesn't
look like it likes you very much.
Go back to training after eating.
Zhou Yang,
there are so many delicious foods.
Eat with us.
Come on, take off your shoes.
Fine.
Eat together.
Hello, Dr. Qin.
Fu Binian,
your recovery
is better than expected.
[You should be able to]
[do daily exercise.]
[Keep it up.]
Thank you, Dr. Qin.
I'll keep working hard.
Goodbye.
Nice shot!
Zhou Yang said you're good
at basketball.
But I didn't believe it until now.
I haven't played for a long time.
I'd like to ask you for advice.
About what?
Some training plans.
Did you make all of these?
I'm the captain.
I know them
better than the coach.
Actually, Lin Qingyuan
is a bit troublesome.
The others are fine.
What?
Is there a problem?
Nothing.
I'm just relieved for Zhou Yang.
What do you mean?
How about this?
I'll give you a training plan.
What plan?
Today's training is simple.
Running up the mountain.
Running up the mountain?
Simple?
How can this be simple?
Just run up, right?
If we start this late,
we'll be up there after dark!
Then it all depends
on how fast you can run.
Today's goal is simple:
beat the sunset.
You must reach the viewing platform
before dark.
Over.
I'm not done yet.
Today is not a team race,
but an individual orienteering.
Here's the map.
Thank you, coach.
Warm up well before you set off.
The sun is strong up there, so be sure to apply sunscreen.
Don't get sunburned.
Thank you, coach.
Remember to turn on
the location-sharing app.
Make sure you understand your own route.
Keep an eye on each other.
Don't let anyone fall behind.
Thank you.
Alright, alright.
Don't dawdle.
It'll be dark soon.
Let's go.
Okay.
Each map
has a different route.
Some are difficult, some are easy.
All are tailored for you.
Remember,
individual orienteering
is not about who is the best,
but the overall result of the team.
As long as one person
doesn't arrive on time,
the whole team will have extra training tonight.